[Music]
yo kids really far away at your [ __ ]
booth checks the sacristan must occur at
the incident going to find themselves
this is so [ __ ] up
why are we the ones that do all the work
in this house
it's not fair we should be playing games
and having fun oh it's not so bad really
it gets me in the Christmas spirit and
after we are done we can eat gingerbread
cookies that's right bro and you know
how I love me some cookies
so put that cute butt to work you butt
wrap it stop fighting you two huh hey
what the [ __ ] I've never seen this photo
before it looks like a photo of us but
why is it all torn up there's a lot of
stuff in here it must be really old I'll
say check out this picture of Uncle
Chuck Jesus Christ he used to look like
that
Goddamn he could [ __ ] my ass any day hey
guys do you think there might be a
picture of our Father in here
[ __ ] [ __ ] enough messing around let's
get back to work but bro don't you want
the truth there are more boxes in here
if we find the right one we could learn
more about how her father stopped it we
have no father he left us when we were
poopy baby [ __ ]
it's best to just do what mama says and
forget about it bro do you truly feel
nothing at all
of course I do every single day of my
Goddamn life
I can't even count how many times I
cried in my bed after a bad day just
wishing and hoping daddy would come home
to hold me but he never did
neither of you say anything c'mon got it
we don't want her beating our ass again
and as for that photo bro I know what
you're thinking but put it back whatever
[ __ ]
hey mama we're done in the Attic can we
have some cookies now goodness that was
quick
you're just in time for dinner so take a
seat we are having chili Frito pie
stirrer night so I hope you are hungry
so cool I freaking love frito chili pies
Uncle Chuck did you hear we are having
frito chili pies tonight aren't you
excited
boy nobody in the-- so silicon chichi
frito appears except for yo even Sonya
today sucked in leaked acetic acid so
your oil and our tourists enter your
clinic Arab nobody liquors yo how many
times do I have to tell you kids not to
go through the [ __ ] in the Attic [ __ ] it
looks like I gonna have to spank you
like a little [ __ ] again
Charles give me your belt get that [ __ ]
out of my face
tell us right now about our dad I'm not
telling you anything you [ __ ] [ __ ]
there is nothing to say who else was in
that photo with us and why is everything
upstairs destroyed what are you hiding
from us
please mama I'm begging you tell me why
my daddy left maybe he left because you
are nothing but a little [ __ ] Manic I'm
so sorry I didn't mean that you always
think you're hot [ __ ] but you know what
I'm the top [ __ ] around here I hate you
I'm going to my room and never coming
out good because you aren't getting any
dinner tonight anyways nice going donkey
oops now we don't get frito chili pies
like I give a [ __ ] why don't you go
crying to mom
if you feel like being a whiny baby what
the [ __ ] Sonia why do you have food mom
said we couldn't mom likes me best so
she said I could have some as long as I
don't give you any
take these spoons I got em from the
kitchen by hiding them in my butt crack
Manek can I see that photo for a minute
huh
Oh xiu'er go right ahead
you know it hasn't snowed even once and
Christmas is just a few days away would
and bringing in dad home for Christmas
totally be the best present for momma
ever
then how about we go look for him on the
back of this photo look do you see this
message it has a number and address on
it unfortunately the phone number
doesn't work anymore
but the address leads to a famous
photographer maybe if we can find him we
can get answers about how our father are
you for real that's awesome who better
to ask than the very man who took his
photo then it's settled
while mom and uncle Chuck are having
dinner we will set out to find father
kids I brought you some hot cocoa
I see you are still mad at me Manic it's
fine I don't blame you
if you don't want to talk but you must
understand there are reasons why I must
keep these things from you kids sure
oh why would your fatty your planet in
thought that is conversation your
respond to an adult yo-yo wish boy what
age this is host appeal
Elena deaf a Tony vote away
Sonia and Monica gone too
man there's a lot of people here isn't
there look over there
it's our only friends hey everyone
perfect you all made it Manic what took
your green bean looking at so long did
you stop to take a smelly crap sorry
about that
we had to sneak out of the window window
what the [ __ ] are you say on the phone
you told me we were going to the new
PlayStation 4 but calls a Nintendo and
Xbox are for [ __ ] we have something
even better than that show him says our
father was in the picture but it has
been torn out so now we're on an
adventure to find him it's almost
Christmas I should be eating fruit cakes
and drinking eggnog until I poop my
pants don't pull me into your fucked-up
family story
please Knuckles you have to help us even
Sonic is in so much pain nothing would
make his Christmas better than to bring
our father home Oh [ __ ] are you
lonesome not with you by my side oh look
at you acting so tough I promise you
[ __ ] I will make this the best
Christmas ever
just you wait where are those stupid ass
[ __ ] hey Sonia
isn't that your sexy uncle oh my God
Loretta yari
hit them yo Tokyo : promotion don't let
him touch your butt what's going on
why is your uncle chasing us is he
finally trying to rape you I don't know
but if he catches us it's all over just
run and don't look back Hari Charles
they're going to get away yo can throw
at me
everybody inside them that's Aviva
let go of me you creep we'll be back in
two weeks and when we do we will have to
add with us
[Music]
he [ __ ] put down that book I need to
ask you a question what question could
you possibly have to interrupt i
Knuckles the cool Echidna I call and hit
but notice that you are the only one
here who didn't compliment me on my new
lipstick why is that are you gay are you
a [ __ ] [ __ ] gay ass [ __ ] this
lipstick cost me $300 where are your
Goddamn manners listen I didn't even
know you were with our group I thought
you were Jared Leto from Suicide Squad
Jade Lee I don't even know who the [ __ ]
that is what I do know is that this
makeup is very expensive and for you not
to acknowledge how sexy it makes me well
it's just plain mean of you you want to
know what I think you slit people like
you disgust me it's not the makeup you
rub on your face and butt crack true
beauty comes from the inside do you
think anyone really cares that you have
big boobies hell no [ __ ] the plastic
surgery you constantly get on your ass
it just made it look like you ate
bowling balls if you really want people
to like you how about you fix your
attitude first but cause I ain't got
time for stuck-up [ __ ]
you know what I'm not through talking
with you your ass is so [ __ ] big that
when you stepped on the train it smack
the kid in the face you talk like that
is a bad thing
everybody loves touching my ass you
don't understand you kill that boy butt
cheeks slammed into him with great forth
how do you think his parents are going
to feel when they realize their son is
never coming home
you should be ashamed of yourself I I
never thought of it that way
typical of a [ __ ] all you think about is
yourself
yo Mindy baby why you looking so sad for
a sad face doesn't fit such a sexy [ __ ]
oh Manic he said I look like I'd lead oh
and so did the Train Dre and the worst
part of it is I don't even know who that
is
well I mean you kind of do but who is he
I never heard of the shed Leto before in
my life that's because you're too busy
being a [ __ ] [ __ ] he's the main
character of ahead DC movie Suicide
Squad here luckily I always carry a
photo of him around wherever I go just
don't put it in your butt haha sorry
Manning but you can trick me this is
just a photo of me I mean look at all
that makeup no Mindy look closely
way to wash down minute this isn't me
who who is this that's Jared Leto baby I
keep that photo in my pocket because he
has green hair like me Manic do I really
look like this Mindy why do you think
when we have roleplay sex you're always
the Joker how could you say such things
to me Manic I taught you what my
boyfriend that is it from this day
forward we are over Manic Hedgehog Mindy
please wait fine you know what I don't
need you [ __ ]
[Music]
you
some are saying that the photographer
studio is all the way out here in the
forest yeah I don't know about this are
you shooting he lives out here [ __ ]
that's what it says on his website his
house is on the other side of the forest
right on the edge of a cliff overlooking
the ocean come on you guys are thinking
too much into it
the man is old he probably just moved
out here to get away from it all now
let's go
the sooner we meet him the sooner we can
find out where our daddy is my bro is
right everybody let's make like a bunch
of bananas and split come on BART levy
[Music]
fart levy what's wrong don't you want to
come with me to learn about my daddy
[Music]
Beach this is your journey not mine this
is something that you should face by
Yosa you've been looking for your daddy
your entire life and now you have a
chance to find him what you're about to
find may be life-changing it's not my
place to be there when it happens you
always rely on me to do everything but
now it's time to use your own strength
but Bart levy I don't have any strength
I rely on you so much because because I
need you I'm I'm [ __ ] weak I'm
nothing without you Bart levy that's why
I need you there that's not true it was
your decision to come all the way here
to find him was it not if you ask me
that alone is a sign of how strong you
are now go on your daddy might be
waiting for you just as you are waiting
to see him I'll be waiting right here
for you when you get back ready to spank
your cute little ass
Bart levy thank you I'll be back as soon
as possible so please wait for me
[Music]
Master Bart levy forgive me but I
couldn't help but overhear elfrid I
thought I told you to go wait at the
airport I understand I will go there
right away but first I must know why are
you making Sonic go through this you're
the richest man alive surely with your
money and information you could find
Sonic's father without all this work
could it be that that you don't want
Sonic to find his father if I may ask is
it the cause of the relationship you had
with your father that you're afraid for
Sonic
do you think this is the place it was
appointed for walk from the road don't
you think [ __ ] it has to be the taxi
driver said that are really famous
photographer lives up here yet but he
also said eight little boys wound up
missing in this part of the forest in
the past week
the door is open silly you can come
right on in I'm just taking a [ __ ] but
I'll be right out
damn [ __ ] I've been waiting for you
what took you so long I was so bored I
already started slathering my nipples
with whipped cream how about you get
over here and start licking it off like
a good [ __ ] huh you're not my
four-year-old nephew who the hell are
you or well I don't give a [ __ ] who you
are the fact that you're alone means
there's no one here to stop me from
being whatever the hell I want
oh oh I see you're not alone um ignore
what I just said what are you all doing
here we are here to ask you about Howard
AD we are the children of Queen Aleena
we found this photo that you took of our
parents when they were younger if the
message on the back is anything to go by
you really knew our dad didn't you
so the three of you are the children of
Queen Aleena I can see the family
resemblance yes I did take that photo I
guess you could say that I'm a family
friend speaking of which how is your
uncle Chuck doing I haven't seen him
since he forcefully spanked my sister's
ass and got arrested he's the greatest
uncle ever he took us to the mall last
week and bought us chicken nuggets you
blew brother seems to have gotten a lot
of looks from his uncle no wonder he's
so sexy IFS taking all of my strength
not to throw him over the table and [ __ ]
his [ __ ] riot here speaking of which
do you think you could turn around for
me for a second
like this Wow your butt is so big you
really are your father's son I can still
remember the day that time at your
father he got into a huge fistfight in
my front lawn and got knocked the [ __ ]
out it was even before the three of you
were born
well honey today is the day you are
finally going to meet my father don't be
too nervous he's not so bad
unless your rocket is because would
listen before you all the other rivers
in else totally awesome it is both check
sorry okay whatever yo go mingle Domingo
neutral is a variable for big man and if
they catch a co-starring it which way up
yoga's OC log yesterday already Charles
stop trying to scare him
don't listen to my stupid brother you're
gonna do fine thomna face fast quickly
act not so your attorney wants to marry
my daughter
ooh he wat si yo rock Latino team boot a
little bit sh watermark is your teens yo
reward a note for me Delta let alone a
mean Ocean Alto he say you are aware
inert you enemy kutis it at last yo hot
rod Dustin music I totally Loretta truth
hey yo know what yo my own Road
reservoir theory it in educated on who
Stephanie what's your favorite a
Vocaloid miniskirt herbs ear open me cut
costing not eight
place a host an eatery a little bit on
here it's almost over
what the book what are you checking out
me as hosting that's it put a man WAP
bish
[Music]
Wow so this entire Beach belongs to you
you must be rich as [ __ ] I wonder how
much you would pay to [ __ ] me in the ass
oh you naughty little [ __ ] don't play
dumb we all know you let me [ __ ] you in
the ass for free
a big fat ads like yours is just
screaming for attention it's saying
spank me daddy spank me spank me hard
punish me daddy
damn he is really going to town on her
ass just imagine his skill in the
bedroom hey old man maybe you should
consider sexual harassing somebody your
own age instead of you know my [ __ ]
girlfriend girlfriend we broke up
remember or have you already come
crawling back like a [ __ ] if I want to
seventy year old man grew up in my ass
that's my choice whatever hey old man
are you going to tell us who our father
is or what that's right I suppose I
should tell you about him I kept you all
waiting long enough for starters his
name is damn that you've got a big ass
son of a [ __ ]
bro are you out of your [ __ ] mind
just hold on I've got you I won't let
you fall you little shits you better not
let me fall [ __ ] this is your fault
[Music]
tell us well or daddies which I ain't
telling you [ __ ]
until you pull me back up tell us and
we'll pull you up all we wanted a name
damn it bro I don't think I can hold him
for much longer the poop in his pants
just added about 20 more pounds please
no I don't want today
[Music]
you
kids where the ever-loving [ __ ] did you
go we're sorry mama
we tried to get home sooner but we
didn't think we would be away for so
long
do you have any idea how worried I was I
probably [ __ ] my pants eight times out
of fear of what might happen to you kids
so what a studly blemish that your went
talking about that we never found him no
matter how hard we looked we just
couldn't find daddy but on our journey
we found something else something
greater and what you said that your
phone followed we found out that we
don't need a dad in our lives to be
happy
you see [ __ ] you are so caught up in
looking at the future that you want with
your death that you completely ignored
the family and friends that have been
with you all along you shouldn't waste
your time looking for somebody who
doesn't want to be found but instead
spending time with those who make you
happy new friends are the best family
the tanne body could ever have in the
world it's as they say friends are the
family we make along the way
I don't need it end to be heavy
especially one who walked out on someone
as great as my mom you're right Sonic
we were always jealous of other people
because they had two parents when in
reality it's dad who should be jealous
of us the cause with our friends we have
the best family ever even better than if
he was here I am an akai just gotta see
the way you push that by with the cliff
was really cool you were so manly well
what I'm trying to say is do you want to
get back to they I guess so it looks
like you couldn't stay away from Daddy
too long you sexy [ __ ]
Manic Manic what's wrong
it's nothing glad to have you back sugar
tits come on everybody we're going to
take a family photo everybody gather
around
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
Oh is the place in your heart where
memories
[Music]
[Applause]
you
damn it
damn it all I can't believe they pushed
me off the cliff I could have died what
the group of [ __ ] hey what's that
upon that hilltop there's there's
somebody standing up there who are you
please can you come down here and help
me I am hurt
wait no there isn't just one there is
more people coming up were they
thank you thank you so much for finding
me I am hurt very bad who did this
failure was it them then what do you
mean by them shut up
we're the ones asking the questions here
do you understand that [ __ ] you aren't
wearing any pants right now it wouldn't
take much effort to [ __ ] you in the ass
so I suggest you cooperate if you want
to live okay okay I'll tell you
everything just don't shoot we saw Sonic
the Hedgehog and his family talking with
you earlier what they hell did they want
with they only wanted to meet me because
I took a family photo for their parents
long ago that's it
I'm not lying to you what do you guys
think it doesn't seem like he's lying to
us you're right
he doesn't but even still as long as he
lives the Hedgehogs have an ally we must
kill him no you can't do this we had a
deal I'm gonna enjoy this
don't shoot him yet I wish to speak with
him
[Music]
greetings so you are the one who spoke
with Sonic the Hedgehog today which
waited the go for you at least do the
honors of telling me who you are before
I spill the beans on that day I went
into that haunted house when I went in I
had everything a beautiful wife a son
and everything I could ever dream of but
when I came out I lost it all my wife my
son my money everything all the cause of
one man enough for you my name is not
important I have dedicated my life to
getting revenge against Uncle Chuck and
his family and not just them but their
friends as well every single one of them
all of our lives have been ruined and
they are to blame for that but who just
who the hell are all of you you can call
us the boys
together we will defeat the sounding
Underground now come let us go you're
not going to kill me
no because you two have been hurt by
Sonic and his friends we are willing to
give you an offer in one week's time you
will join us if not it means you have
sided with them and you also will die
choose wisely [ __ ]